坦纳 福斯特
车手
拉特利奇 伍德
专家
亚当 费拉拉
破坏王
翻译   淳屌丝   socoollike
当你听到超跑这个词 你常常会想到欧洲
When you think supercars, you tend to think European.
但不久之前 可不是这样的
But not so long ago, it was a different story.
请原谅我脸上的夸张笑容
Please excuse the gigantic grin on my face right now
因为我现在驾驶的是...
because I am driving a car
我儿时梦寐以求的车子
I dreamed of just getting close to my entire childhood...
极速240迈、纯美国制造的Vector W8
The 240-mile-per-hour all-American Vector W8.
1990年问世 W8是第一台能够与...
Born in 1990, the W8 was the first U.S. supercar that could compete
兰博基尼和法拉利之流竞争的美国车
with the likes of Lamborghini and Ferrari.
这辆车的发布对美国有着重大意义
It was so big for America to come out with a car like this...
它告诉欧洲人 "你知道 我们不怕你"
To tell the Europeans, "you know, we're not afraid.
我们也能造超跑 甚至比你们更好"
We can do this, and we can do it even better."
但它马上就没落了
And then it was gone.
发生了什么
So, what happened?
为什么没有美国超跑
Why is there no American supercar?
W8在1993年工厂倒闭后就停产了
W8 production stopped in 1993 after the company faltered,
只生产了19台
and only 19 were ever made.
看上去美国的超跑梦破灭了
It seemed like the American supercar dream was dead.
但在美国其他地方
But across the country,
一些小手工作坊让梦想继续延续
a few boutique manufacturers have kept the dream alive.
为了看看这些土生土长的超跑究竟如何
So to find out how good these homegrown supercars are,
我们每人挑选了一辆
we each chose our favorite
驾驶它们与欧洲竞争者进行测试
and put them to the test against their European rivals.
我去
Holy...
Top Gear让我们驾驶美国超跑...
"Top Gear" told us to drive our American supercars
前往加州马利布市的起点处
to the starting point in Malibu, California.
为了看看谁选的车最好
To see who had the best one,
我们将完成一系列挑战
we'd be competing in challenges,
拉特的第一个挑战是...
and Rut's first challenge
从他的车里爬出来
was just to get out of the damn car.
你还好吗 老爹
You all right, big daddy?
- 搞定   - 好的
- Got it! - Okay.
搞定
Got it.
我们需要那种椅子
We could get, like, one of those chairs
可以把人抬起来
that gets people up the stairs.
对 就像他们把海豚...
Yeah. You know, like, when they move the big dolphins
从一个水族馆挪到另一个
from one aquarium to the other.
对 像吊床一样的东西
Yeah, like a cradle thing.
向它背上洒水
You just squirt water on his back.
- 保持湿润   - 对 把它拉过来
- Keep him moist. - Yeah, pull him around there.
我刚刚驾驶了一辆萨林S7 你敢相信？
Can you believe that I'm driving a Saleen S7?
它大概有10岁了
It might have been 10 years old,
但对我来说 S7是完美的美国超跑
but, to me, the S7 is the perfect American supercar...
自然吸气的V8爆发出650匹马力
Naturally aspirated V8, 650-horsepower,
四分之一英里用时10秒 2003年的售价为三十七万五千美元
10-second quarter mile, and $375,000 back in 2003.
它那赛车式的设计...
And its racecar design
让它在160迈时有足够的下压力
means that it creates enough downforce at 160 miles an hour,
相当于它自身重量 它可以翻过来开
creates its weight... It could drive upside down.
试试看啊 我可不相信
- Do it. - I don't believe you.
我听过很多次了
I've heard that stat so many times
但没人能做到
about so many amazing cars, and nobody's done it.
我跟你们讲
Let me tell you something.
我把车翻过来开好多次了
I've been upside down in a car many times.
你不会想那样做的
You don't want to do it.
那是什么
What's that?
- 我好像见过那台车   - 是的
- I feel like I've seen that car before. - You have.
我选择了罗森Q1
I've chosen the Rossion Q1.
罗森公司买断了noble M400的生产权
Rossion bought the rights to the noble M400,
把它变得更高端大气上档次
added luxury and refinement, but still kept
仍保留了赛车的功重比
the power-to-weight ratio of a track car.
只要十万美元 你就能得到一辆拥有450匹马力、
For 100 grand, you get 450 horsepower in a car
总重不到2500磅的车子
that weighs less than 2,500 pounds.
- 你死定了   - 我死定了？
You are dead. I'm dead?!
你还开那辆呢
You're driving that.
这是Lucra 你们所见到的...
This is a Lucra. Gentlemen, what you're looking at
是美国工艺的代表作
is a manifestation of American ingenuity.
连挡风都没有
Without a windshield.
对 在手册上没看到 但问题不大
Yeah, I didn't see that in the brochure, but it's cool.
虽然我的Lucra LC470没有车顶
Sure, my Lucra LC470 didn't have a roof,
但它有一台7升的V8引擎爆发出500多匹马力
but it did have a 7-liter v8, generating over 500 horsepower,
而车子只有两千磅重
the car weighing just 2,000 pounds,
售价只要十三万五千美元
and all that for just 135 grand.
酷毙了
This is pretty cool.
这就是一台酷酷的Miata
It's a cool-looking Miata, though.
它一点也不像Miata
This looks nothing like a Miata.
我喜欢在侧排气管上的商标
I like that it has the logo here on the side pipes,
当你出来时
so that way, when you get out,
就会把商标印在你的裤腿上
it'll brand the car's logo right on your calves.
不管是不是Miata 我们要出发了
Miata or not, it was time to start our journey.
我们要行驶100英里到达莫哈韦沙漠里的...
We were told to head 100 miles to an automotive proving ground
一个汽车试验场
in the Mojave desert.
胜者将驾驶一辆三十万美元的汽车
The winner would get his hands on a $300,000 dream car.
出发了 伙伴们
Mount up, gentlemen.
我们要去沙漠了
We're heading to the desert.
你带防晒霜了吗
Do you have sunscreen in there?
不 我有车顶 还要防晒霜干嘛
No, I got a roof. Why would I have sunscreen?
哈哈
Ha ha!
哦 我的老天啊
Oh, my goodness gracious.
每次 每次
Each time. Each time. Oh, wow.
在前往莫哈韦沙漠的路上 我们听了一场...
As we headed to Mojave, we were given a lecture
关于"怎样成为超跑"的演讲
on what makes a supercar by the human fly.
它必须别具一格
It's got to be fairly exclusive.
它必须非常快
It's got to be very fast.
它必须由专注的驾驶员...
It's got to take a concentrated hand
来释放它的动力
to extract the most out of it.
它的全部潜力...
And its performance potential
无法被大多数车手所激发
has to be out of reach for most drivers.
它还要做的就是...
Oh, what it also needs to do is inspire
调动车手的情感
some sort of emotion from the driver.
能够满足一位汽车爱好者的热情
It needs to feed the addiction that you have as a car enthusiast.
我之所以挑选这辆车是因为...
I picked this car because I really...
哦 好大一块石头
Ooh That was a big rock.
是因为我想知道...
I picked this car 'cause I really wanted to know
当它刚上市时...
if it could live up to all the hype
那些杂志天花乱坠的宣传是否属实
that the magazines gave it when it first came out.
现在我得承认
Now, I'll admit,
这辆车的驾驶体验非常扣人心弦
the driving experience of this car is really intense.
你得真正地去驾驶它
This is something that you really have to drive.
而不是随随便便地
You're not just kind of driving it.
这是一种紧张的驾驶过程
It is a full, intense driving session.
当拉特全神贯注时
While Rut was busy concentrating,
亚当有点困惑
Adam was getting confused.
当你抬起油门时
When you lift off the gas,
会发出这种排气口的声音
that's either the exhaust note burbling
或者是车子的颠簸声
or the car's crumbling.
我不太确定
I'm not quite sure.
前往试验场的路线
Our route to the proving grounds
要从洛杉矶穿越到比华利山
took us across Los Angeles to Beverly hills.
现在该进行第一个挑战了
And it was time for the first challenge.
定义超跑的标准之一就是...
One of the defining features of supercars is their ability
能否拥有超高的回头率
to turn heads with their stunning looks.
为了看看谁的回头率最高
To find out which of ours stood out the most,
我们要把车停在罗迪欧大道上 看看谁的车子...
we had to park on rodeo drive and see which one of our cars
在十分钟内被拍照的次数最多
had the most photographs taken in 10 minutes.
你吓到小朋友了
You just scared a kid.
你刚刚吓到小朋友了
You just scared a kid officially.
右边的小孩跳了起来 摸了摸心脏
This kid to your right jumped. Bless his heart.
你还好吗
Are you okay? You okay?
这是个吓人的野兽 还能说什么呢
It's a scary beast. What can I say?
延着街道前进 我们遇到了个竞争对手
But just down the street, we had some competition.
史上最伟大的超跑之一
It was one of the greatest supercars ever made...
一百七十万美元的布加迪威龙SS
The $1.7 million Bugatti Veyron SS.
我们的车子要怎么跟它比呢
How would our cars do up against that?
哇 那辆布加迪可真帅
Wow. I'll say that bugatti looks pretty good.
臭虫小子先上
Bug boy was up first.
好 这里已经有一群人了
Okay, there's already a crowd formed here.
不敢相信
Unbelievable.
他需要主题乐 是吗
He needs theme music, doesn't he?
他需要围巾和皮头盔
He needs a scarf and a leather helmet.
好 计时开始
Okay. Count it.
零七分了 他有十分钟
It's 7 after. He's got 10 minutes.
他在干嘛
What's he doing? What's he doing?
他来了
Here he comes. Here he comes.
很酷的护目镜
Cool goggles.
很帅啊 你去滑雪了吗
That's neat. Were you skiing?
哦 护目镜
Oh. Goggles.
你刚滑雪回来吗
Were you just snowboarding?
你做电焊多久了
How long have you been welding?
好 目前为止我看到八个人
All right, so thus far, I see eight people.
- 什么   - 最多九个
What? Maybe nine.
你应该这么数 5, 10, 15, 20, 25, 30, 35...
Okay, you got to count by 5, 10, 15, 20, 25, 30, 35...
停下
Stop it!
那是站着的人 不是拍照的人
Those are people standing, not people taking pictures.
只有八...九个人在拍照
There's only eight... there's nine people taking pictures.
那他们干嘛站在那儿
Why are they standing there?
别的人站在那儿是因为...
The other people are just standing there
他们无法相信那玩意也能开到这儿
'cause they can't believe that that thing made it.
时间到
And that's time.
时间到了 就是这些
Time. That's it.
87个
87.
- 好吧 25个   - 25张照片
All right. 25. 25 pictures.
你以为很多了？
You think that's something,
等着我的萨林吧
wait till I pull the Saleen around.
好 去吧
Okay. Go.
萨林这么帅的赛车造型
With the Saleen's racecar styling,
让我很有信心
I was feeling confident.
那位女士好像在说 "需要我帮你出来吗"
Look at... this other lady is like, "can I help you get out?"
他们在拍他摔倒的照片
They're taking a picture of him falling out.
他们在拍他的股沟
They just got a picture of his plumber crack.
你们好 你好
Hey, how you doing? Hey.
你知道吗 目前唯一的照片...
You know, so far the only photograph
是你倒在地上的样子
has been of you falling on the ground.
那...是...一个前滚翻
It was a tuck and roll.
我停车的时候就有两个拍照了 那也算上
I got two as I was pulling in, so count that.
两个？无所谓
Two? Whatever.
人群都涌向它
Look at them just flocking to it.
他们在想 "这是辆布加迪吗"
They're thinking, "ooh, is this a bugatti?"
- 不   - 看 看
No. Look. Look.
他让他的儿子与车合影了
He just got his son in the picture with him.
他又拍了一张
Oh, now he's going for the other.
六分钟过后 我的萨林...
Six minutes in and my Saleen
像蜂蜜吸引蜜蜂一样 吸引着人群
was drawing people in like bees to honey.
老实说 虽然我的照片更多
I would say that I had more photos,
但你的照片都是走到门前...
but your photos are actually going up to the door
与车合影
and taking a picture with it.
高质
Quality.
我的照片都是高质量的
I'm getting quality pictures right now.
可惜的是 这不算是挑战的一部分
Too bad that wasn't part of the challenge.
- 停表吧   - 多少
Stop the clock. What's the time?
大概20个
That's like 20.
好 你是20个
Okay, so you got 20.
好 你是25个 我是20个
All right, 25 for you, 20 for me.
还不错
Respectable.
你不可能超过我们的
There's no chance you can beat that.
在这等儿着 准备学着点吧
Wait right here, gentlemen. Watch and learn.
你看 那东西长得真无聊
Look at that... How boring that thing looks.
就像新一代的MR2
I mean, it looks like a new-age mr2.
没错
That's exactly right.
没有一个人站在旁边
Not a single person standing around it.
你去过那边的陛尚精品店吗
Have you ever seen Bijan down there?
天呐 那地方太疯狂了
Oh, my gosh, that place is insane.
- 难以置信   - 开始计时吧
Unbelievable. Start the clock.
陛尚里到处是黄色
A lot of yellow in Bijan.
我们在找话题聊天
We're trying to find something to talk about
因为没人在你的车边上
because there is nobody around your car.
开什么玩笑 快看
Are you kidding? Look at that!
没人
Nobody.
真的没有一个人在拍照
There's literally not a single person taking a picture.
你们知道为什么吗
You know why?
因为它很低调 好吗
- It's understated. - All right?
人们走过之后
People are gonna walk by and go...
第二眼看到它 会说 "哇 我竟然没看到它
On the second look, they'll go, "wow, I had no idea!
罗森耶"
Rossion!"
"哦 一辆MR2"才不会那样呢
- "Oh, an mr2!" - No, I don't think so.
我觉得他们根本不会那么说
I don't feel like they're gonna say that at all.
情况不太妙
It wasn't going very well,
于是我决定使用我的斗篷装置
so I activated my cloaking device.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你们知道那边停着一辆罗森Q1吗
Did you know there's a Rossion Q1 right up the block?
没错 我可以看到你们的表情
Yes! I can see it on your faces.
你们很惊讶 去吧 去看看它
You're amazed. Go ahead. Go take a look at it.
一辆鲜活的罗森Q1
A Rossion Q1 live in the flesh.
开启了斗篷装置
With the cloaking device activated,
情况有所好转
things began to look up.
看看他们 看到没
Look at them looking. See that?
为什么这么多人从陛尚里过来了
What's this crowd of people coming over from Bijan?
看 他们都过来了
See? Look. They're all coming over.
他们都聚集过来
Look. Look at them gathering around.
奏效了
Word's getting out.
继续看吧 随便拍
Go ahead! Enjoy! Take all you want!
这是辆罗森Q1
It's a Rossion! Q1!
我已经超过25了 我赢了
I'm over 25. I'm the winner.
我的罗森赢得了挑战
With my Rossion winning the day,
我们离开比华利山
we left Beverly hills behind
前往莫哈韦沙漠里的试验场
and headed to the Mojave desert proving ground.
让我觉得S7很酷的是...
What makes the S7 so cool to me
它只是史提夫·萨林的一个想法
is that this was just an idea that Steve Saleen had.
他是位成功的肌肉赛车手
He'd been successful racing mustangs,
他与福特关系很好
he had a great relationship with Ford,
他决定用美国的方式来诠释...
and he decided to make an American interpretation
欧洲超跑
of a European supercar.
从图纸到成品用了18个月
It went from paper to a working car in 18 months.
在这三辆车中
And if you look at these three cars,
它向超跑的尝试是最出色的
it's hands down the best attempt at a supercar here.
罗森Q1是由noble M400改的
The Rossion Q1 is based on the noble M400.
当noble公司不打算再制造它时
When noble decided they're not making anymore of them,
罗森买下了知识产权 制造Q1
Rossion bought the intellectual property and built the Q1.
他们想制造一辆你可以天天使用的超跑
They wanted to make a supercar you could use every day.
所以他们对内饰花了很多心思
So they really paid attention to the interior,
加入了更多的高端皮革、电动车窗
adding more leather and Alcantara®, power windows,
以及奢侈至极的...手套盒
and the ultimate in luxury... a glove box.
从驾驶体验上看 他们在赛道与日常使用间...
As far as the ride, they seem to have struck a good balance
达到了很好的平衡
between track performance and daily driver.
悬挂不是很硬
The suspension is not spine-crushing.
甚至有点舒服
It's kind of comfortable.
我保证我现在坐得比坦纳舒服
And I guarantee I'm having a better ride than Tanner is.
看看他
Look at him back there.
他就像个卡通人物
He looks like a cartoon character.
你在后面晒得怎么样啊
Are you just baking in the sun back there?
你还好吗
Are you okay, man?
你说什么
What did you say?
这灰尘真烦人
The freakin' dirt is insane.
试验场很酷的一点就是...
The cool thing about a proving ground is that it's a place
你要去那儿证明一些东西
where you go to prove stuff,
你要把车子推到极限
where you get to push things to the limit.
最终我们要让它觉醒
Finally, we get to open this baby up.
我知道它马力很强 我知道它轻如鸿毛
I know it's got a ton of power. I know it weighs nothing.
有点蠕动的感觉
It feels a little squirmy,
但我等不及带它到赛道上尝试
but I can't wait to get it on a road course and find out.
我们来到了老旧的本田试验场
We arrived at the old Honda proving grounds.
建于1990年 占地四千英亩
Built in 1990, the facility stretches over 4,000 acres,
它有一条五英里长的直道
and it has a 5-mile road course, straightaways,
7.5英里的环形道
and a 7-1/2 mile oval.
这地方真酷
How cool is this place?
我很多年前就想来这儿了
I've wanted to come here for years.
你可不会在这里挖出...
It's not like there's old Honda engines buried in the dirt
老的本田引擎什么的
or something that you're gonna find, you know.
别告诉他啊 你让他的梦想破灭了
Don't tell him that. You're ruining the magic for him.
看看这儿 我们可以完全释放它们
Look at this. We can open these things up.
没错
Hell yes.
我们要干什么
What are we gonna do with them?
一台好的超跑要有迅雷不及掩耳的加速
A good supercar promises lightning-quick acceleration,
为了看看哪辆美国车是最快的
so, to see which one of our American cars was the quickest,
我们要来一场百公里加速赛
we're going to have a race... Zero to 60.
- 百公里加速   - 三车并行
- Zero to 60? - Three wide.
没错
Hell yeah.
没问题
Not a problem at all.
真是个白痴
What an absolute dork.
天啊
Oh, gosh.
开始吧
Let's go for it.
先生们
Gentlemen...
三
In 3...
二
2...
一
1...
走
Go!
稍后
Coming up,
我们和欧洲对手正面对决
we go head-to-head with the Europeans...
快 亚当
Come on, Adam!
我们中的一个
...And one of us gets to put
有机会测试30万美金的肌肉车
a $300,000 muscle car to the test.
我们在莫哈维沙漠
We were in the Mojave desert
比赛看看谁有最好的美国超跑
competing to see who had the best American supercar.
我的Rossion赢得了拍照比赛
My Rossion won the photo challenge,
现在是0到60加速比赛
and now it was a zero-to-60 race.
倒数 三
In 3...
二
2...
一
1...
出发
Go!
哦 我的轮胎打滑了
Oh, my tires are spinning.
60 到了 60
60! There it is. 60.
我一骑绝尘
I smoked them the whole way.
太轻松了 小伙伴们
Well, that was easy. Yeah, buddy.
我轮胎打滑了 我起步没起好
I was spinning the tires. I didn't get a good launch.
怎么了 拉特
What happened, Rut?
马力太大了
There's so much power, it just...
一直在打滑
It spun the tires all the way.
你到60的时候刹车了吗 是的
- Did you stop when you hit 60? - Yeah.
这东西一档就能到65迈
This thing goes 65 in first gear.
我根本不用换挡
I didn't have to shift at all.
我就一直加到转速限制 然后踩的刹车
I just went right up to the rev limit and then hit the brakes.
我是说这就意味着Lucrs
I mean, this basically means that the Lucra
有击败欧洲对手的潜质
could potentially take on the Europeans,
但是你们那些我就不确定了
but those guys I don't know.
我听不见
I can't hear.
我是说
Basically, it means...
我听不见你
I can't hear ya!
Lucra可以击败欧洲对手
That the Lucra could take on the Europeans.
不论他们能不能听见我
Whether or not they could hear me,
我轻松地赢得了比赛
I easily won the challenge.
现在我和亚当各胜一场
So with one victory each for Adam and I,
我们前往测试场的另一侧
we drove off to the other side of the proving grounds
去接受下一个挑战
for our next challenge.
先生们 我们下方是本田试验场里...
Gentlemen, we are standing above the longest straightaway
最长的直道
here at the Honda proving ground.
是的 大概有1.2英里长的直道
Yeah, I think it's 1.2 miles from turn to turn.
好的 我们要做什么
Okay. What are we doing here?
很高兴你问了
I'm glad you asked.
哦 好的
Oh, yeah.
现代欧洲超跑引以为豪的
"Contemporary European supercars pride themselves
是他们的做工质量
"on their build quality
并且可以安全地到达极速
"and ability to safely reach their claimed top speeds.
为了测试你们的车能否做到同样水准
"To see if your cars can do the same,
你们要在一英里内
"you will each have a mile
加速到你们车子自称的最高时速
"to hit your vehicles' claimed top speeds.
最接近的人获胜
Closest to the top speed wins."
好的
Okay.
我的是200英里每小时
I mean, mine goes 200 miles an hour.
我的也是
So does mine.
就那个 没有风挡
In that? No windshield.
你会带头盔吗
Are you gonna wear a helmet?
是的 我要带
Yeah. I'm gonna wear a helmet.
好 主要是为了防虫子
- Good. - Just for the bugs, mainly.
好的 你的极速是200英里
Okay, so your top speed is 200 even?
是的 他们是这么说的
Yeah, that's what they say.
你的呢
What's your top speed?
187 先生们
187, gentlemen.
我觉得我有优势
I think I have an advantage for this one.
因为你要达到
'Cause you have to get...
187英里
To 187 in a mile.
13英里 看 我自己算出来的
- 13. - See that? - By myself.
你做了数学 是的
- You did the math? - Yeah.
慢13英里每小时
13 miles an hour slower.
因为这有整一英里
Since it's a standing mile,
这就离终点有2/10的距离
and this is about two tenths away from the end,
我想我们应该在这待着 你去弄个头盔
I think we should stay here and you should get a helmet.
我同意
I think you're right.
毫无疑问 这回很吓人
This, have no doubt, is going to be very scary.
100英里的时速 没有风挡
No windshield at 100 miles an hour.
如果你骑过摩托车 非常夸张
If you've ever ridden a motorcycle, it is extreme.
但是摩托车上你有头盔
But with a motorcycle, you have a helmet,
幸运的是 我确实有一个
and, luckily, I do have one of those.
我的意思是 这不仅仅是为了...
I mean, this isn't just about, you know,
你能把右边的那个踏板踩的多狠
how hard you can press the right pedal,
而是你要去踩右边的那个踏板
it's about the thing that makes you press the right pedal.
胆子
His balls.
不 他的脑子 我是要说他的脑子
No, his brain. I was gonna say his brain.
好的 让我点火 她启动了
All right, let me fire it up. She's running.
100了
That's 100!
他来了
Here he comes.
130!
已经三档了 三档
Third gear already. Third gear.
140!
150!
160!
真快
That's quick.
162英里每小时
162 miles an hour.
太疯狂了
That was insanity!
哦 我的天
Oh, my gosh!
真是太快了
- That was fast. - That was fast.
亲妈呀 真是太吵了
Holy crimine. That was loud.
头保住了
Still has a head.
让我从这东西里出去
Get me out of this thing.
看到有多疯狂了吧
How freaking crazy was that?
你还好?
You okay?
你没事吧
You all right?
我感觉自己刚去了崔健的演唱会
I feel like I just went to a Motley Crue concert.
耳朵已经聋了
That was deafening.
我85迈的时候就失去听力了
I think I lost hearing at about 85.
你过去的时候像个晃头小人
You went by like a bobble head was driving it.
你开了多快
So, how fast did you go?
162.
哇哦 什么
- Wow. - What?
是的 真是快
Yeah. That's fast.
这就意味着我要超过162
Well, this means I've got to beat 162
因为我的车据说也能跑200英里每小时
since my car also says it'll do 200 miles an hour.
咻 去吧
Whew. Go get 'em.
让我们出发
Let's do it.
真是危险
That was dangerous.
真是即可怕又有趣
That was scary. And fun.
我的Lucra达到了162英里每小时
My Lucra's 162-mile-per-hour run
比极速慢了38英里
was 38 short of its claimed top speed,
不过对于1英里来说不算慢
but not bad for just one mile.
现在该看拉特如何驾驭超跑了
Now it was time to see how Rut would handle supercar speed.
他肯定会吓尿的
He's gonna freak out.
他肯定会说"我的天" 一定是这样的
He's gonna go, "oh, my God!" And that's gonna be it.
哇哇哇 我有孩子
"W-w-w-whoa! I got kids!"
我有孩子 我不能做这个
"I got kids! I can't do..."
我在想我的妻儿
All I'm thinking about is my wife and kids.
想我们晚饭能吃些什么
Maybe what we're gonna have for dinner,
想怎么为我媳妇庆祝下周的生日
what we're gonna do next week for my wife's birthday.
但是我要先对着那个桥有多快开多快
And I've got to drive as fast as I can towards this bridge.
好的 准备好了吗 大个
All right, you ready, big fella?
开始吧
Let's do this.
哦好的
Oh, yeah.
好的 来吧
All right, bring it, big daddy.
出发 200英里每小时的超跑
Here we go. 200 miles an hour in a supercar.
好的 一档
All right, there's first gear. Okay.
慢慢来
Nice and easy there.
好的
Okay.
开始有些发飘了 100了
Oh, it's starting to float around a little bit. That's 100.
他来了 他来了
Here he comes. Here he is.
红色小火箭
Just a little red rocket.
120 130
Oh, that's 120, 130.
140.
我去
Holy...
Holy sh...
160.
减速 伙伴
Slow down there, big guy.
尼玛呀 真叫快
Slap your mama, that is fast.
哇哈 半箱油用掉了
Whoo, I just used a half a tank of gas.
我160迈的比坦纳慢了2英里
My speed of 160 was 2 miles per hour slower than Tanner's.
因为亚当的极速只有187英里
Since Adam's top speed was only 187,
他只要到148就可以胜利
he'd only have to reach 148 to win.
亚当 我们已经完成了任务 该你了
Adam, we've made our peace. Have you?
准备好了
I'm ready.
出发 我的天
And go. Good lord.
好的 我们走
Okay. Here we go.
稍后 亚当是死是活
Coming up, will Adam live or die?
我们在莫哈维沙漠
We were in the Mojave desert
测试三辆美国超跑
testing three American supercars.
亚当和我各自赢得一场比赛
Adam and I had each won a challenge
我们正试图达到最高速
and we were now trying to reach our cars' top speed.
我到了162 哦吼吼
I hit 162... Whoo-hoo-hoo!
拉特到了160
...Rut hit 160...
现在该亚当出发了
...And now it was Adam's turn.
出发 我的神
And go. Good lord.
好的 我们走
Okay. Here we go.
出发
There we go.
起步不错
Good launch.
加油 宝贝
Come on, baby.
萨林是全程都很安静吗
Was the Saleen just quiet the whole time
然后开始叫喊
until you just started, "rawr"? Just...
你喊的比萨林响
That's louder than the Saleen.
超过100了
Over 100.
110.
120.
他已经开始颠了
He's moving around with it already.
他还在加速
He's going for it.
五档了
That's it right there.
已经够快了 亚当
That's fast enough, Adam.
加油 宝贝 加速
Come on, baby. Get up there!
挺住 加油
Grab some of it! Let's go.
130.
够快了
Fast enough.
140.
145 哦!
145. Ohh!
真快呀
That was quick.
是的 我是说 真快
Yeah, that... I mean, that seemed fast.
开萨林的时候我没在这
I wasn't up here for the Saleen, obviously,
但是他真快
but he was booking it.
萨林更红一些
The Saleen was More red.
怎么样
How was it?
真有意思
It was fun.
是的 多快
Yeah? How fast?
145 哦
145. Oh!
yes 等一下
Yes! Wait.
是百分比 你们很接近
It's a percentage. See, you were closer.
等等 好的!
Oh, wait. Yes!
跳吧 跳吧
Do the dance. Do the dance.
不 我不需要
No, I don't need to. I didn't stretch.
但我们知道Lucra又赢了
But I think we established that somehow the Lucra, again,
它比那些更加超跑
is more of a supercar than those things.
你还知道吗 除非下雨
You know what? Unless it rains.
下一个是什么 我听够了
What's next? I've heard enough.
很不错 我们走
That's nice. Let's roll.
你觉得可能下雨? 我们在沙漠了
You think it's gonna rain? We're in the desert.
好消息是 我出汗了
The nice thing is, I'm so sweaty
我一直往座椅下滑
I'm just really sliding in the car now.
坦纳已经两胜我的Rossion了
With Tanner leading two wins to my Rossion's one,
所以我就要赢得下一个比赛
it was down to me to win the next challenge
逼平比分
and force a tie-breaker.
最后的比赛就在
That challenge would take place
数英里以外的赛道
on a road course a few miles away,
给我们机会表现
which gave us a chance to reflect
我们车子的能力
on how our cars were shaping up.
也许现在比较难开
It may be hard to drive at times.
也许不是路上最快的车
It may not be the fastest supercar on the road.
但你知道吗
But you know what?
我仍然认为它是辆好车
I still think this is a brilliant car.
是公路上的猛兽吗? 是的
Is it a beast on the road? Yeah, it is.
想想看
I mean, think about it.
S7R拿下了勒芒
The S7R won le mans.
我的基本上就是调低的版本
I'm basically in a tuned-down version of that car.
所以前面没有跃马标志
So it doesn't have the little prancing horse on the front.
没有以牛来命名 没什么大不了
It wasn't named after a bull. Big deal.
不会改变我爱这辆车的事实
It doesn't change the fact that I still love this car.
而且如果钱不是问题 我一定来一台
And if money was no object, I'd own one.
即便取得胜利
Despite his victories,
Lucra还是不能说服坦纳
Tanner was less convinced by the Lucra.
老实讲
I'll be honest.
2000磅505马力
For being 2,000 pounds and 505 horsepower,
这东西的加速确实很好
this thing certainly is good at accelerating.
不过只要动动方向盘我就能告诉你
But I can tell just by jerking the wheel back and forth
这东西到了弯道绝对是噩梦
that it is gonna be a nightmare in a corner.
前部实在太活跃了
It's just that the front end moves so willingly.
前悬挂非常的扎实
The front suspension is really good.
但是尾部
But the back end
根本不知道在做什么
doesn't necessarily have a clue what's up.
但是
But holy crap...
太尼玛有趣了
Is it fun.
我坦白
I'll be honest.
我对Rossion很失望
I'm getting a little disappointed with the Rossion.
有一种自制改装车的感觉
We have this kind of homemade-y kind of kit-car-ish,
我在后院做的 改自另一辆车
"I made it in the backyard. It's based on this other car."
这就是拼凑而成的
We're frankensteining stuff together.
如果美国人真想
If America was seriously considering
进入超跑的游戏
getting into the supercar game,
为什么不做一台中置引擎克尔维特
why don't they make a mid-engine corvette?
造一台可以与法拉利媲美的野兽
Just build a beast to go up against Ferrari.
我们要做得就是致力去做
I think we just got to commit ourselves and do it.
目前为止 我们的美国超跑表现得很好
So far, our American supercars had performed pretty well
令人印象深刻的0-60加速
with impressive zero to 60 times
和一英里极速的尝试
and strong top-speed attempts over a mile,
但是我们都是独自进行的
but we'd been testing in isolation.
现在是真正考验他们的时刻了
Now it was time to find out how good they really were,
这就意味着带来意大利和德国对手
and that meant bringing on two Italians and a German...
40万美金V12 艾文塔多
The $400,000 v-12 Aventador,
兰博基尼有史以来造过最好的一辆
one of the best Lamborghinis ever made;
15万美金保时捷911 GT3 RS
the $150,000 Porsche 911 GT3 RS,
全世界操控最好的车之一
one of the best-handling sports cars in the world;
和 23万美金法拉利458 意大利
and the $230,000 Ferrari 458 Italia,
2009年一发售便成为经典
an instant classic when it was launched in 2009.
为了测试我们车的综合操控
As a test of our cars' overall handling,
我们要和它们在一条充斥着各种弯道的...
we'd each race one of them over a 2-mile road course
两英里的赛道上比赛
packed full of twists and turns.
亚当决定第一个出发
Adam had decided to go first.
所以你要让rossion对法拉利458
So, you're gonna put the Rossion up against the Ferrari 458,
550匹的终极超跑
a 550-horsepower amazing supercar.
也是这一代最好的超跑
Arguably one of the better supercars built in our generation.
非常理解 先生们
Totally understood, gentlemen.
458不仅仅是超跑 是一个成就
The 458's not a supercar. It's an achievement.
难道我们束手就擒吗
What are you gonna do, lay down?
你晚上睡得着吗
You don't go gentle into that good night.
你要的是愤怒的死亡之夜
You rage against the dying of the light.
我去 随你便
Wow. Whatever.
两台车 一个人
Two cars, one driver.
不是
No.
两台车 两个人
Two cars, two drivers.
这就是 我们的希望
Well, there goes all hope.
一定很惨
This is gonna suck.
这边请 试替哥
Right this way, stig.
随后亚当有了一个好点子
Then Adam had an unusually bright idea.
这不合理
This doesn't make any sense.
亚当 有个问题 说
- Uh, Adam, question. - Yeah.
为什么他在rossion里面
- Why's he in the Rossion? - Look.
这是为美国车而战 对不
This is a fight about American supercars, right?
这个国家的希望不是我
Well, the best shot the country has ain't me.
而是他
It's him.
为了国家的利益牺牲自己
Sacrifice yourself for the good of the nation.
我喜欢
I like it.
我不是为了我们 先生们
I'm not doing this for us, gentlemen.
我这么做是为了美利坚合众国
I'm doing this for the United States of America.
法拉利都不会知道是怎么输的
Ferrari's never gonna know what hit it.
好的 亚当 万事俱备 准备好了?
All right. Adam, thumbs up, you ready?
试替哥 无所谓了
Stig, whatever.
我们走 倒数 3 2 1
Here we go. In three, two, one.
出发
Go!
法拉利出发了 哦 哦
Ferrari gets it off the line! Oh! Oh!
试替哥第一个弯要延迟刹车
The stig's gonna outbrake in the first corner.
哦 试替哥真是飞过去的
Wow! The stig just blew right by me.
他来了 我输了
There he goes. I'm losing!
我输了 但是我赢了 但是我们赢了
I'm losing! But I'm win... But we're winning!
这个其实可以说通
This actually makes sense.
亚当给了车子胜利的机会
Adam's giving that car a fighting chance
因为458在数据上更好 是的
- 'cause the 458's a better car on paper, right? - Uh, yeah.
我希望rossion赢 但是不想看起来很糟糕
I want the Rossion to win, but I don't want to look bad.
你觉得会很接近吗
Do you think it's gonna be close?
呃 不
Well, no. I...
我觉得试替哥会秒了他
No, I think that stig's gonna walk him.
他可是试替哥
He's the stig.
哦 那走线真干净
Oh, this part's tight.
他来了 试替哥 我的天
Here he comes, the stig. Oh, my gosh!
快 亚当 快
Come on, Adam! Come on!
快 快 快 快
Go! Go, go, go!
一点也不接近
That wasn't even close at all.
这就意味着rossion很快
That means the Rossion's pretty quick.
哈哈 亲们 我输了我们赢了
Ha ha! Fellas, I lost and we won!
我不知道什么意思 不过我觉得是好事
I don't know what that means, but I think this is all good.
不 你知道吗 你的主意不错
No, you know what? You had a good idea.
我也用这招 下一个是我
I'm gonna follow suit. Way to go.
美国1 欧洲0
It was America 1, Europe zero.
我要用兰博基尼打败试替哥
I'm gonna try to beat the stig in a Lamborghini Aventador
700匹的四轮驱动
with 700 all-wheel-drive horsepower.
他在萨林里
There he is in the Saleen.
我是说 我希望车赢 所以这就是我在这个车里的原因
I mean, I want that car to win, which is why I'm in this one.
但也是因为
But I also did this
我非常想开艾文塔多
because I really want to drive an Aventador.
嘿 拉特 里面感觉怎么样
Hey, Rut, how you feeling in there?
唯一能让沙漠更热的办法
The only way to make this desert hotter
就是坐在一台黑色的车里
is to get in a black car.
好的 先生 准备好了吗
Okay, gentlemen. Are we ready?
我准备好了
I'm ready.
我们走
Here we go
倒数 3 2 1
in three, two, one, go!
快 拉特
Come on, Rut!
哦 我在第一个弯之前还领先
Whoo, I'm holding off the stig in the first turn!
兰博四驱的马力让
The power of the all-wheel-drive in the lambo
试替哥只能在后面
is keeping the stig at bay.
不错 不错 非常厉害
All right. All right, that was impressive.
他还是领先
He's still leading.
进入第二个弯还是领先
Still leading going into the second corner.
我在做什么
What am I doing?
我怎么会跑在试替哥前面 真疯狂
Why did I pull in front of the stig? That's crazy.
哦 亲 哦
Whoa, man! Ohh!
好的 这就是了
Oh, right, there I go.
哦 你现在是几档 哦 哦 哦
Oh, what gear are you in? Oh, oh, oh!
哦 换挡拨片 我用反了
Oh, the panels shift. I went the wrong way.
哦 我的天
Oh, my gosh!
700马力真是不可思议
700 horsepower in this car is amazing.
萨林已经领先很多了
It's a pretty big lead with the Saleen.
他来了
Here he comes.
萨林赢了
The Saleen's got it!
他们来了 S7领先
Here they come, man. The S7 is in the lead.
艾文塔多过去了
And the Aventador passes through.
看 很完美
See? It's perfect.
拉特输了 美国赢了
Rut loses, America wins.
所以拉特输了 耶
- So, Rut loses... - Yeah.
在埃文塔顿
In the Aventador,
因为他比试替哥开的慢
but because he's a slower driver than the stig,
S7就先过线了
the S7 happens across the line first.
我想应该竖大拇指 是不错吧?
I think it's a thumbs up. Is it a thumbs up?
好样的
Great job!
输的好
Good job losing!
稍后 这一场景我已经...
Coming up, it's something I've wanted to see
期待很久了 坦纳vs试替哥
for a long time... Tanner versus the stig.
我们的美国超跑迎来最后的挑战
It was the final challenge for our American supercars,
与欧洲竞争对手正面交锋
a head-to-head race against their European rivals.
为了让我们的车有更大几率获胜
To give our cars the best chance of winning,
亚当和我让试替哥代驾 结果奏效了
Adam and I had the stig drive, and it worked.
现在坦纳的Lucra要对阵保时捷
Now Tanner's Lucra was up against the Porsche.
公平起见 由试替哥驾驶Lucra
To keep it consistent, the stig would drive the Lucra.
如果坦纳想要自己的车获胜 他就得放弃荣誉
While Tanner wanted his car to win, he had his pride.
这并不意味着我要放水
It's not like me to just not go out and try to win.
在直道上 跟它比会有点吃力
On the straightaways, it's gonna be hard to hang with that thing.
但在弯道和刹车方面
But in the corners and braking,
那可是保时捷的拿手好戏
that's what Porsche is legendary for.
那就是GT3 RS所擅长的
That is what the GT3 RS is all about.
今天 它将成为Lucra的终结者
And today, it could be a Lucra-eating machine.
你觉得试替哥真的是达妮卡·帕特里克？(性感女车手)
You think it's true stig's Danica Patrick?
可能
Could be.
好 坦纳 你准备好了吗
All right, Tanner. You ready?
好了
Ready here.
试替哥 我默认你已经准备好了
Stig, I'm just gonna assume you're ready
你都不鸟我一下
and not acknowledge me at all.
好 准备
- Okay. Here we go. - Here we go.
三 二 一 走
In three, two, one, go!
哦 起步差不多
Oh, it's a pretty even start.
哦 他超过去了
Oh, he's gone.
那台Lucra可真快
Oh! That Lucra is fast.
我要从外线超越
I'm taking him on the outside!
坦纳又领先了
Oh, Tanner's in front again!
他就在后面
Oh, he's right on me!
我挡住他了
Oh, now I'm holding him up.
这可不好
This is bad.
在弯道我可以超过他
In the corners, I can get him.
但每次到直道
But on every single straightaway,
他又追回来了
he just bites back.
Lucra 他到处漂
Oh, the Lucra! He's sliding everywhere.
试替哥很认真啊
The stig is really working for it.
Lucra的动力爆发了 不好
Oh, the power of the Lucra! Oh, no!
我喜欢它 但我又讨厌它
I love it, but I hate it!
他来了 他超过我了
There he goes. He squirted in front of me.
试替哥超过他了
Oh, the stig's got him.
那么多的马力可真快啊
It's so fast with all that horsepower!
难以置信
It's unbelievable!
我在弯道可以追上他
I'm gaining on him in the corner.
我可以在最后的弯道前超过他
I can get him before the last turn.
这两个家伙都不松油门的
This is two dudes that don't lift professionally.
直接冲过弯道
Steer through it.
他们来了 他们来了
Here they come. Here they come.
他在猛打方向盘
Oh, he's really sawing at the wheel.
不 Lucra赢了
No! The Lucra takes it!
太帅了
That was awesome!
我们站在这作死啊
Why are we standing here?
不知道
I don't know.
怎么样
How was it?
- 感觉很卑鄙   - 为什么
I feel dirty. Why?
因为有点像是我赢了
I mean, I know that it's kind of a win...
- 对   - 但是我输了
Yes. ...But I lost.
好消息是
Here's the good news.
你输了 美国赢了
You lost, America won, gentlemen.
你得承认 这些美国车很酷
You have to admit... these American cars are cool,
但它们还有很长的路要走
but they still have a long way to go.
比如 你会选这辆还是Lucra？
For example, would you not still choose this over the Lucra?
其实...如果你想要可靠性的话
Well... well, if you're gonna rely on it
日常使用的话 当然...
on a daily basis, of course.
你会选择458还是罗森
Would you choose the 458 over the Rossion?
开一整天都没事
All day long, baby.
奇怪的是
Now, here's the weird thing.
我还是会选择萨林 而不是Aventador
I'd still choose that Saleen over the Aventador.
我觉得Aventador是辆上等的超跑
I realize that the Aventador's a superior car.
我知道 但我不在乎
I get that, but I don't care.
有时这才是超跑的内涵
Sometimes that's what a supercar's about.
就是说 "你知道吗 我不在乎"
It's about saying, "you know what? I don't care."
我们学到了什么
So, what'd we learn here?
我觉得我们学到了...
I think we learned
美国超跑所做的尝试很酷
that the American supercars' attempts are cool.
很酷的车子
They're cool cars.
但要想与欧洲超跑竞争...
But they've got a long way to go
他们还有很长的路要走
to try to compete with the European supercar.
不 这不是我想到的
No. Not what I was actually getting at.
我们学到的是——我赢了
What we learned here is that I won.
我喜欢
Love it.
- 他说的对   - 没错
That's true. Yeah.
这可不是我学到的
I mean, that's not what I learned.
我也没学到
I didn't learn that, either.
我懂
I knew that.
小心 要烧胎了
Yeah. Wait. Here comes the burning.
在证明了我的美国超跑是最好的之后
After proving that my American supercar was best,
我要享受战利品了
I was off to claim my prize.
这是另一台高性能跑车
It was another high-performance car.
相较于超跑 它更有肌肉车的味道
This one was a little more muscle than supercar.
当你听到"梅赛德斯"
When you think "Mercedes,"
你会想到精致、
you think of words like refinement...
优雅、
Elegance...
保守的中产阶级会计
Conservative mid-level accountants.
最近 他们肯定遇到了中年危机
But recently, they must have had some sort of midlife crisis,
便用那滑稽的德国小烟斗...
put something in that funny little German pipe
抽起烟来
and smoked it.
不像比尔·克林顿 他们确实吸了(克林顿大麻梗)
But unlike Bill Clinton, they inhaled
因为他们制造了这个
because they've gone and made this.
这是梅赛德斯SLS AMG黑系
This is the Mercedes SLS amg black series.
没错 它是亮黄色的
And, yes, it is bright yellow.
"黑"是他们给那些...
Black is the name they give
高性能车的特别高性能版本...
to the very special performance versions
所取的名字
of their performance cars.
它也名副其实
And it lives up to its name
这辆三十万美元的车子坏得让你爱不释手
'cause this $300,000 car is very bad in a very good way.
好 我们走
Okay, here we go.
这辆SLS的第一项肌肉测试
The first test of the muscle-car credentials of the SLS
必须是百公里加速了
had to be a zero-to-60 run.
百公里加速3.6秒 极速198迈
Zero to 60 in 3.6 seconds, 198 mile-an-hour top speed,
声浪超乎想象
and the sound is unbelievable!
这是辆梅赛德斯？
This is a Mercedes?
推力就像货运火车一样 太棒了
It just pulls like a freight train, and it's glorious!
德国没有限速 所以他们能好好享受它了
The Germans have no speed limit so they can enjoy this stuff.
老天啊 为什么我们没有不限速的高速公路
Good lord, why don't we have autobahns?
称之为肌肉车有点荒谬
Seems a little ridiculous to call it a muscle car,
但你想想看
but if you think about it,
这辆SLS已经有了V-8这个喷火猛兽
the SLS already started out as a v-8 fire-breathing monster.
AMG又把它改装得到处是碳纤维
Then amg put carbon fiber everywhere,
扩大了排气口 改成铝质
opened up the exhaust, made it out of titanium,
减轻了150磅 让它更快
lost 150 pounds on the car... Making it faster.
这是许多工厂所做的事情
It's what a lot of companies do here
比如shelby, Saleen, hennessy 增加马力 减轻重量
like shelby, Saleen, hennessy... Add power, lose weight.
就是这么简单
It's simple, really.
所以 SLS在这儿就像在家里一样
So, the SLS black will be right at home
转速爆表
revving at a red light
行驶在凌晨两点的美国街头
on main street, U.S.A., at 2:00 A.M.
但那也是所有...
But that's where the similarities
美国肌肉车的终点
with the all-American muscle cars end.
梅赛德斯以高科技的创新...
Mercedes prides themselves on high-tech innovation
和高额的研发经费而自豪
and limitless research budgets.
这就意味这辆肌肉车应该可以做...
That means that this muscle car should be able to do
其他肌肉车做不到的事情
what other muscle cars can't do...
高速过弯
Corner at high speed.
为了找到答案 我前往高山
So, to find out, I headed for the hills.
这儿 女士们先生们 这才是公路
And this, ladies and gentlemen, this is a proper road.
加州南部的74号高速
Southern California's highway 74,
把普通肌肉车当早餐
which eats ordinary muscle cars for breakfast.
稍后 我将试驾SLS黑系...
Coming up, I put the SLS black series to the test
尝试在10分钟内...
when I try to cover 10 miles
通过全美最危险公路之一的10英里路程
of one of America's most dangerous roads in less than 10 minutes.
我们来到加州沙漠
We've been in the California desert
看看谁选的美国超跑最好
competing over which was the best American supercar.
我的Lucra赢了 这意味着...
My Lucra had won, and that meant
我将试驾德国肌肉车——梅赛德斯SLS AMG黑系
I got to drive a German muscle car... Mercedes SLS AMG black.
它在直道上已经证明了自己
It had proven itself in a straight line,
现在我要在一段十英里的自杀公路上
but now I was going to test its cornering ability
测试它的弯道性能
in a 10-mile suicide run
遍布发卡弯和一百英尺的悬崖
with hairpin bends and 100-foot dropoffs.
为了让挑战更有趣
And to make it interesting,
我要在十分钟之内完成
I was gonna try to do it in less than 10 minutes,
也就是说平均每分钟要开一英里
which would mean averaging at least a mile a minute.
好 在我面前 是一段十英里的狭窄崎岖山路
Okay. Ahead of me, we have 10 miles of twisty, gnarly road.
为了应对 我们有碳陶瓷刹车
But against that, we have carbon ceramic brakes.
我们有622匹马力
We have 622 horsepower.
我们有上千名梅赛德斯和AMG的工程师...
We have thousands of Mercedes and AMG engineers
建造的机器 只为了做一件事...
who built a machine to do one thing,
把十英里的山路一口吞下
and that is to devour that 10 miles in one gulp.
不要让我太得意
And stop me if I'm smiling too much.
准备
Here we go.
出发了
And we're off!
老天啊
Good lord!
我在做一件非常危险的事
I'm doing something so dangerous!
我喜欢
I love it!
感觉我在驾驶一条黄色巨龙
Feel like I'm riding a giant yellow dragon
通过地狱之门
through the gates of hell.
三英里过后 我达到了75迈的平均速度
3 miles in and I'd managed to average 75 miles an hour.
我的计划超前了
I was ahead of schedule.
我要赶时间
Now we're getting after it.
牵引力控制系统完全关闭了
Traction control is completely off.
只有少数电子元件在工作
Still a few electronics going on with a...
天啊 你好 ABS
Oh, my gosh. Hello, ABS
近况如何
How's your day going?
感觉我正在打破物理定律
It felt like I was breaking the laws of physics.
我已经开了六英里了
I was already 6 miles in
时间还剩下四分多钟
and still had over four minutes on the clock.
但群山没有放弃
But the mountain wasn't giving up.
它要动真格 它请来了萧敬腾
It wanted blood, and it called in the rain gods.
下雨了 路况不太理想
Now, rainy conditions, of course, are not ideal,
特别是用着晴胎
especially when working with dry-weather tires
它必须有足够的温度才行
that like to be right up to temperature.
但是潮湿路面...
But the wet is a place
能够让你真正地窥探一辆车的裙底
where you really look under the skirt of a car
看看里面究竟有什么...别想歪了
and really see what it's about... not to be too graphic.
不管是晴是雨 已经没有退路了
Rain or not, there's no turning back now.
别忘了 黄色代表着危险
Don't forget, yellow is the color for danger.
这颠簸的路面、这淅沥的小雨 黄色就对了
This bumpy road...And this rain... it's the right color.
老天啊
Good God!
天啊 高速时太难过弯了
Oh, God. It is just the twitchiest thing at speed.
我不确定这是不是...
I'm not sure if it's just a problem
轮胎抓地力所造成的问题
coping with the amount of grip that the tires create or what,
但这真尼玛吓人
but [Bleep] It's scary.
我还有一英里 雨拖慢了我
I had a mile to go, but the rain had slowed things down
我必须在一分钟内完成
so I had to cover it in less than a minute.
最后的弯道
Here's the last turn.
我成功了
I had done it.
不敢相信SLS打败了时间
Incredibly, the SLS had managed to beat the clock.
在这样的速度和路况下行驶
Driving at these speeds and these conditions
如果开的是普通的车子
in your average car
这可能是你最后一次开车了
would most likely be your last time behind the wheel.
但梅赛德斯让不可能变成可能
But Mercedes has made it possible.
这不是一辆普通的车
And this is not a simple car.
它原始 它纯粹
It's raw. It's pure.
但还是由电脑控制着
But it still is electronically controlled.
当你抬起油门时 会有一丝犹豫
There's a little hesitation when you lift off the throttle.
这些控制...
There is controls
成为驾驶体验的一部分
that are always a part of your driving experience.
本质上讲 梅赛德斯制造了...
So, essentially, what Mercedes has built
地球上最聪明的肌肉车
is about the smartest muscle car on the planet.
SLS黑系确实是一项...
The SLS black is, indeed,
卓越而惊人的成就
a stunning and outrageous achievement
不只是因为它那全能的性能表现
not just because of its all-in-one performance package
更是因为它代表了大公司...
but more because it represents that big car companies
仍然有着推动汽车产业...
still have the desire in what they can do
技术革新的欲望
when they want to push the automotive envelope.
这让我又回想到美国的超跑
And that brings me back to the American supercar.
小手工作坊竭尽所能...
Boutique shops are doing their best
在世界舞台上竞争 而汽车三巨头们又在干嘛呢
to compete on a world scale, but what about the big three?
福特GT发布、成为世界级的超跑
It's been since 2004 when the Ford gt came out
那已经是2004年的事情了
as a world-beating supercar that we've done that.
道奇、雪佛兰、福特 来吧
Dodge, Chevy, Ford, come on.
我们准备好了
We are ready.